Newland/Zeuner Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music of Charles Zeuner (Box 48-57)
  - Instruction and study materials (Box 56)
    - [Miscellaneous cover pages, fragments and scraps] (Box 56)
Koehler, Henry
17 • Air de Deux Petits Savoyards: Ascouta Jeannette [Dalayrac] varié pour la flute seule par Köhler.
17 • Sonata concertante pour le Piano Forte et flute composée par Henry Koehler. Oeuvre 97.
Kreutzer, Conradin
11 • Ouverturen für das Piano-Forte solo. Nro. 53 - Das Nachtlager von Granada von Conr. Kreutzer.
Kreutzer, Rodolphe
15 • 40 Etudes ou Caprices pour le Violon par R. Kreutzer.
Krommer, Franz
27 • Missa Solemnis in C, op. 108. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland
Küffner, Joseph
18 • Drey Quartetten für 2 Violinen, Bratsche & Violoncell, von Joseph Küffner. 48tes Werk.
Kuhlau, Friedrich
41 • Deutsche Gesänge mit Begleitung des Piano-Forte von Friedrich Kuhlau. 19tes Werk, 2te Samml. Lieder.
20 • Quartetto, Op. 50
8 • Sonatinas, Op. 55
Kuhn
27 • Messe Solennelle. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland
Labarre, Théodore
18 • Duo pour harpe et piano sur des motifs de L'Eclair de F. Halevy composé par T. Labarre. Op. 86
Labitzky, Joseph
23 • Elfen Waltz
23 • Woronzow Waltzes
Lambillotte, Louis
35 • Ave Maria
32 • Memorare
33 • O cor amoris
33 • O Gloriosa Domina
27 • Pascale Mass
33 • Quid retribuam
33 • Regina coeli
34 • Tantum Ergo
34 • Te Deum
Lamparelli, Antoine
41 • Romances avec accompagnement de Piano ou Harpe tirées du Roman de Sabina, musique de Lamparelli.
Lampugnani, Giovanni Baptista
44 • Quintetto. No. 4. (Il villan che colti vail giardino)
Lederer, Joseph
27 • Et in Spiritum Sanctum [from Masses No. 2,4,5,6]
27 • Mass [in D]; Gloria, Sanctus, Agnus Dei
27 • Mass No. 1 (1781)
27 • Mass No. 2 (1781)
27 • Mass No. 3, in G
27 • Six Masses. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland
Lejeal, Alois F.
27 • Mass in D
• Mass. => see: Weber, Mass in G, Box 29
Linley, Thomas
41 • Carnival of Venice
41 • In My Pleasant Native Plains. Composed by Mr. Linley.
Lumbye, Hans Christian
8 • Eine Sommernacht in Dänemark
Lutgen, Paul
31 • Alma Redemptoris Mater
Luzzi, Luigi
31 • Ave Maria
Marpurg, Friedrich Wilhelm
56 • Abhandlung von der Fuge - Exempel
Martin y Soler, Vicente
8 • [L'Arbore de Diana]
41 • Baum der Diana. Aria. Doristo. Nro. 4.
41 • Lilla. Aria. Warum ward mir nicht vergennet von V. Martin. Nro. 20.
11 • Overtura per il Clavicembalo dell'Opera Una Cosa rara Del Sig. V. Martin.
17 • Una Cosa rara, Operette par Martin arrangée pour Deux Flutes Traversieres et Violoncelle par Ehrenfried.
Mascagni
31 • Ave Maria
Mason, Lowell
37 • The Lord our God is clothed with might
Massé, Victor
44 • Le Prix de famille. Opéra Comique en un acte. Paroles de Méry.
Mayseder, Joseph
13 • Duo pour le Pianoforte à 4 mains par Joseph Mayseder. Arrangé d'après le premier Trio pour le Pianoforte, Violon et Violoncelle par Charles Czerny. Oeuvre 34.
Mazzinghi, Joseph
27 • Mass, arr. for 4 voices by W. A. Newland, 1862
Méhul, Etienne Nicolas
22 • Joseph. Overture
Méhul, Etienne-Nicholas
11 • Ouverturen für das Pianoforte. Nro. 33 - Méhul, z. Opera: Joseph.
Meignen, Leopold
39 • [Compilation of sacred and secular vocal works]
42 • L'Attente
47 • L. Meignen's Elements of Vocal Music.
28 • Missa Solemnis
Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix
16 • On the Seashore
13 • Shakespeare's Sommernachtstraum componirt und für das Pianoforte zu vier Händen arrangirt von Felix Mendelssohn Bartholdy. Op. 61, Notturno.
16 • Sweet Souvenir (No. 1, Book 1)
Mercadente, Saverio
22 • Elisa e Claudio. Overture
32 • Jesu Redemptor omnium
28 • Mass in A [transposed from B-flat]
28 • Mass in B-flat. Alto part by W. A. Newland, 1862
• Mass. => see: Millard, Vespers, Box 30
33 • O Jesu Deus
33 • Salve Maria
Meyerbeer, Giacomo
44 • Aus Margherita d'Anjou von Meyer-Beer. (No. I. Beilage zur allgem. musikalischen Zeitung. 1821. No. 2).
Milelotti, G.
39 • La Pentecosta
Millard, Harrison
30 • [Unidentified]
24 • Mass In Bb for four voices, with organ or piano-forte accompaniment, Latin and English text, by Harrison Millard.
28 • Mass in G, No. 1
Miller, Julius
45 • Sechs Canons komischen Inhalts für drei Singstimmen ohne Begleitung componirt von Julius Miller. 2s Werk.
Molinos of Milan
16 • Tema and Variations
Möller, N.
45 • Tio Sånger ur Lucksalighetens Ö satta i Musik och tillegnade Författaren af N. Möller.
Mompour, F. J.
47 • Der allgemeinen Harmonielehre, für angehende Tonkünstler mit ausführlichen Beijspielen, zum Selbstunterrichte, erläutert von F. J. Mompour.
Monti de Rezé, Edouard de
25 • Mass [in B-flat]; Alto added by W. A. Newland
Moore, Thomas
45 • Oh Lady Fair! A Ballad for Three Voices.
Moran, P. K.
39 • The Hebrew Mourner
Mosca, Luigi
42 • Cavatina
Moscheles, Ignaz
8 • Grandes Variations sur la Marche favorite de L'Empereur Alexander I pour le Piano-Forte composées par Ig. Moscheles. Oeuvre 32
Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
21 • [Die Zauberflöte] [Overture - flauto part]
45 • [La Clemenza di Tito]. Duet
28 • [Mass in G]. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland, 1845
8 • [Sonata Collection]
8 • [Waltz]
41 • Abend-empfindung (Abend ist's, die Sonn e ist verschwunden) mit Pianoforte Begleitung von Mozart.
42 • Arias
20 • Concerto. Op. 4.
12 • Cosi fan Tutte - Ouverture. Arrangée pour Clavecin ou Pianoforte.
57 • Die Entführung aus dem Seraglio. Overture.
41 • Die Entführung aus dem Serail Arie. Ach! ich Liebte, war so glücklich, Kannte, etc. (Loin de l'object de ma tendresse) von W. A. Mozart. Clavierauszug.
42 • Die Entführung aus dem Serail. Aria
41 • Die Hochzeit des Figaro
41 • Die Zauberflöte
45 • Die Zauberflöte. Duet - Bei Männern welche Liebe Fühlen. Für das Klavier aus der Opera Die Zauberflöte von Herrn Mozart.
12 • Douze pièces de l'opéra: Figaro de Mozart, arrangées pour le Piano-Forté avec Violon ad libitum.
54 • Glory Be to God on High
12 • Grande Sonate à quatre mains sur un clavecin ou pianoforte par W. A. Mozart. Oeuvre 12. [K 497]
• Jesu, Jesu. => see: Mascagni, Ave Maria, Box 31
28 • Mass in B-flat, No. 7
28 • Mass No. 12
28 • Mass No. 12
19 • No. 3 des cinq principaux Quintetti pour deux Violons, deux Violes & Violoncelle composés par W. A. Mozart.
54 • O God! when thou appearst
• O Jesu Jesu. => see: Haydn, Mass in B-flat, Box 26
2-3 • Oeuvres Complettes de Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart. Cahier III, IV, VII-XI, XIII, XIV, & XVII
12 • Ouverture aus Titus.
13 • Ouverture de l'Opera: La Clemenza di Tito par W. A. Mozart arrangée à quatre mains pour Piano-Forte.
12 • Ouverture du Giovani. Arrangée pour le Clavecin ou Pianoforte Composé par Mr. Mozart.
12 • Ouverture fürs Piano Forte aus der Zauberflöte von W. A. Mozart.
12 • Ouverturen für das Piano-Forté solo. [Nro. 17,18,20,21,22]
13 • Ouvertures de W. A. Mozart arrangées à quatre mains pour Piano-Forté par A. Andre. [No. 2,5,8]
13 • Ouvertures pour Piano-Forté à quatre mains. No. 14 - Mozart, der Schauspieldirector.
8 • Quodlibet pour le Forte-Piano tiré des Oeuvres par W. A. Mozart. Nor. 1
• Requiem à quatre voix. => see: Pergolesi, Stabat Mater, Box 31
41 • Romanze. In Mohrenland gefangen war (Dans un chateau de l'Arragon) von W. A. Mozart. Clavierauszug.
33 • Sancta Maria
4 • Sarah Regina Newland
13 • Sinfonie de W.A. Mozart. [No. 5 in D] arrngée Pour le Pianoforte à quatre mains.
31 • Te Deum a 4 Voci coll accompagnamento di due Violini, Bassi e Organo composto da W. A. Mozart. Partitura mit unterlegtem deutschen Texte von C. A. H. Clodius.
• Te Deum. => see: Haydn, Mass in D, No. 3, Box 26
20 • Trio
16 • Trois Sonates pour le Forte-Piano accompagnés d'un Violon composés par W. A. Mozart. Collection complette Nro. 10.
24 • Twelfth Mass. No. 2 - Gloria in Excelsis.
14 • W. A. Mozart's fünfzehn ausgewählte Sinfonien für das Pianoforte zu vier Händen arrangirt von F. W. Markull. [Nos. 1, 3-8, 11-13]
Müller, August Eberhard
8 • Trois Sonatines progressives pour le Piano-Forte par A. E. Müller. Oeuvre XVIII
Müller, D.
32 • Jesu dulcis memoria, Op. 77
Müller, Wenzel
17 • [Unidentified]
41 • Das neu Sontags Kind. Aria. Wer niemals einen Rausch hat g'habt, für das Clavier von Herrn Müller.
Muzzini
42 • Senti il mio Coro. Sammlung verschiedener Gesänge mit Begleitung des Klavier's. M. Resch.
Naderman, François Joseph
• [Song]. => see: Paer, Romance, Box 42
Natividad
28 • Mass, arr. for 4 voices [by W. A. Newland]
Neukomm, Sigismund Ritter von
31 • Amor Jesu
38 • Canon aus der Ostermorgen von S. Neukomm.(Beilage zur allgemeinen musikalischen eitung.1824. No. III, 20.)
54 • David
56 • David; Chorus - Behold the Giant
31 • Hymnus für drey Stimmen, von Hrn Ritter S. von Neukomm. (Beilage zur allgem. musikal. Zeitung 1825. No. 40; No. III).
39 • O Jesus my Redeemer
Newland, William Augustine
37 • [12] Te Deum[s]
40 • [Te Deum]
30 • [Unidentified]
40 • Fairest Virgin
45 • For our National Celebration July 4th
40 • Grand Te Deum
32 • Libera me Domine
28 • Mass No. 2
28 • Missa Brevis No. I
28 • Missa Pastorale in C, 1858
40 • Te Deum Laudamus
38 • Te Deum Laudamus for four voiceswith an accompaniment for the Organ or Piano Forteby William Augustine Newland.
23 • Villanova College Quick Step
Newland, William Augustine (arranger)
5 • [Unidentified]
5 • Capriccio for organ
• Veni Creator. => see: Liber scriptus, by Ohnewald Box 32
Newland, William Augustine (harmonizer)
34 • Te Deum
Nicholson, Charles
17 • Nicholson's 12 Fants. F. & P. F. No. 5.
Nicolai, Ottous
12 • Il Templario - Sinfonia
Nicolai, Philipp
16 • Il Templario
Novello, Vincent
31 • Asperges
29 • Mass in E for 2 voices, with ad lib tenor by W. A. Newland, 1853
Novello, Vincent (arranger)
31 • Adeste Fideles
Nucci, J. de
16 • Etude en cent variations sur l'accord de FetB pour Violon accompagné d'un second Violon par J. de Nucci.
Ohnewald, J.
30 • [Requiem Mass] No. 2 in B-flat
32 • Exultet orbis
• Iam sol recedit. => see: Liber scriptus, by Ohnewald Box 32
• Iste confessor. => see: Exultet Orbis, by Ohnewald Box 32
32 • Jesu Redemptor omnium
32 • Liber scriptus
Onslow, André Georges Louis
13 • Grande Duo à Quatre Mains pour le Piano-Forté, par Georges Onslow. Op. 7.
Onslow, Georges
19 • Trois Quatuors pour deux Violons, Alto et Basse par G. Onslow. Oeuv. 4, Liv. 1. Nouvelle Ed.
Ostade, Adrian von
8 • Walse aus Adrian von Ostade pour le Piano Forte
Päer, Ferdinando
42 • Achille. Aria
42 • Arias
42 • Camilla. Aria - (In 'quel gentil sembiante).
12 • Ouverturen für das Piano-Forté [Nro. 57,58]
14 • Overture aus der Oper Sophonisbe zu vier Händen für das Piano-Forte eingerichtet Music von F. Pär.
42 • Romance
42 • Sargino. Recit. und Cavatina. Ach Sophie, süsses Leben, ja ich athme nur für dich (Ah Soffie mio caro bene) von Ferd. Pär.
21 • Sofonisbe. Overture de l'Opèra Sofonisbe pour 2 Violons, Alto, Violoncelle, Basse, Flute, 2 Clarinettes, 2 Hautbois, 2 Cors, 2 Bassons, 2 Trompettes et Timballes par Ferd. Paer.
8 • Variations Pour le Piano-Forte Sur une Polonaise de l'Opera: La Griselda, de F. Paër
Paisiello, Giovanni
42 • The Heiress. For Tenderness Form'd, a favorite song in the Heiress composed by Paesiello.
Pecher, W. F.
• O salutaris hostia. => see: Ave Maria (Mascagni)
Pergolesi, Giovanni Battista
35 • Exulta Zion
31 • Stabat [Mater] de Pergolèse. A deux voix avec accompagnement de Piano ou Orgue. Édition deluxe.
Pfeiffer, Theodor
8 • Melodieenbuch Lfg. II. No. 12 - Kathinka-Polka, von Pfeiffer. [and] No. 13 - Das Herzeleid: (Wie i bin verwichen, zu meim Dienderl g'schlichen.)
Phillips, H.
• The Emigrant Ship. => see: Wade, I've Wandered in Dreams, Box 10
Pieltain, P.
19 • Six Quartettos for Two Violins, a Tenor and Violoncello composed by P. Pieltain. Op. 2.
Pleyel, Ignaz
6 • Quintetto 1
16 • Six Duos faciles et progressifs pour Violon et Viola par I. Pleyel. Oeuvr. 48me.
19 • Six Quatuors pour deux Violons, Alto & Violoncelle composés par I. Pleyel. Oeuvre 2d.
13 • Trois Sonates à quatre mains [pour] le Piano-Forte par [J.] Pleyel.
19 • Trois sonates pour Clavecin ou Piano Forte avec Accompagnement d'une Flute ou Violon et Basse Composées par Pleyel. Livre I.
Praeger, H. A. (arranger)
16 • Recollections of Ireland and Scotland arranged for Violin & Piano Forte by H. A. Praeger. No. 1 - The Moreen in G.
Purcell, Henry
45 • Britons Strike Home, a favorite duett composed by Purcel[!]. Arranged for the Piano Forte.
R. D.
42 • The Irresolute Lover. The Words and Music by R. D. Esq.
Raffelin, A.
31 • [Ave verum corpus] A. Raffelin. Partitur.
32 • Ave Regina
35 • Ave Regina
16 • Duetto en un solo violin
29 • Missa brevis in G., with additional tenor by W. A. Newland
33 • O vos omnes
35 • Stabat mater
37 • Villansicos para la Noche de Navidad a 4 voces con acompañamiento de Orquesta (Op. 78)
Rauzzini, Venanzio
42 • The Battle of Maida. Recitative & Song composed by Mr. Rauzzini, Words by Sir George Dallas.
Reeve, William
42 • In the Purse, or Benevolent Tar. The Galley Slave. Composed by Mr. Reeve.
12 • Overture to the Cabinet, as performed at the Theatre Royal Covent Garden composed by W. Reeve.
Rembt, John Ernst
6 • Six trios, 1787
Riebel
13 • Des Marches et des Walses
Ries, Ferdinand
8 • 8me Fantaisie pour le Piano-Forté, sur des thêmes favoris de l'opéra: Zelmira de Rossini composée par F. Ries. Oeurvre 121
8 • Air favori de la Petite Russie varié pour le Piano-Forté, par F. Ries. Oeuvre 56
8 • Divertissement pour le Piano-Forté avec accompagnement d'une Flûte, composé par Ferd. Ries. Oeuvre 62
8 • Douze Bagatelles pour le Piano forte Composeés par Ferd. Ries. Oeuvre 58, Liv. I & II
8 • Fantaisie en forme de rondeau pour le Piano-Forté, sur une Pièce de Mozart, de son Opéra: l'Enlèvement du Sérail par Ferd. Ries
16 • Grand Sonata. Opus 21.
17 • La trente-troisième Sonate pour le Piano-Forté avec accompagnement de Flûte (ad libitum) par Ferd. Ries. Oeuvre 48.
9 • Marche de l'opéra: Tancredi de Rossini variée pour Piano-Forté, par Ferd. Ries. Oeuvre 96. No. 25. des Var.
13 • Polonaise à Quatre mains pour le Pianoforte par Ferd. Ries. Op. 93. 2me.
9 • Rondeau Brillant pour le Piano-Forté, composé sur un thême du H. R. Bishop par Ferd. Ries. Oeuvre 104. No. 3
9 • Rondeau pour le Piano-Forté composé par Ferd. Ries. Oeuvre 106. No. 3
9 • Rondo per il Pianoforte sopra la Cavatina: (Di piacer mi balza il cor) nell opera: La Gazza ladra, di Rossini, composto da Ferd. Ries. Op. 89
9 • Rondo pour le Pianoforte sur la Cavatine de Rossini "Una voce poco fa" ("Frag ich mein beklomen Herz") de l'Opera: le Barbier de Sevilla composé par Ferdin. Ries
9 • Six Exercices pour le Piano-Forté Composés par F. Ries. Oeuvre 31
9 • Trois Airs favoris Variés pour le Piano-Forté, par F. Ries. Oeuvre 82. No. 2 - La Barcarole Vénitienne
9 • Variations sur un célèbre Air Ecossais pour le Pianoforte par Ferd. Ries. Oeuvre 101. No. 1. No. 29 des Variations
Rifaut, V. (arranger)
12 • Ouverture de L'Ambassadrice arrangée par V. Rifaut.
Righini, Vincenzo
54 • Behold & see the goodness of the Lord
Rinck, Johann Christian Heinrich
5 • Nos. 7-10, Rink's Op. 2, 8
Rode, Pierre
19 • Air Varié pour le Violon avec accompagnment d'un second Violon, Alto et Basse par P. Rode. Oeuv. 10.
16 • Rhode's Celebrated Air with Variations, for the Violin.
20 • Second Concerto pour le Violon, par P. Rode.
Roland
23 • Ladies Polka Quadrille [et al]
Romagnesi
• [Song]. => see: Paer, Romance, Box 42
Root, George F.
45 • The Flower Queen, or the Coronation of the Rose. A Cantata in two parts, for the use of singing classes in academies, female seminaries & high schools, adapted especially for concerts, anniversaries, or other festive occasions, and also for the social circle. Poetry by Miss Frances Jane Crosby. Music composed by Geo. F. Root.
Rosenthal, W.
40 • Spirit Creator
Rosewig, Albert H.
30 • [Unidentified]
33 • Regina coeli
Ross, John H.
• Highland Fling. => see: Ladies Hornpipe, Box 16
Rossi
34 • Tantum Ergo
Rossini, Gioacchino
• Ave Maria. => see: Ave Maria by Luzzi (above)
32 • Bone Pastor
16 • Choix de Douze Ouvertures de la composition de Rossini. No. 8 - L'Otello. Arrangées pour le Forte Piano avec accompagnement de Violon ad libitum.
• Domine Deus. => see: Mozart, Mass No. 12, Box 28
43 • Il Barbiera di Siviglia - Cavatina
22 • L'Inganno Felice. Overture
45 • Otello. Duetto
12 • Ouverture de l'Opera: Armida arrangée pour le Piano-Forte musique de J. Rossini.
12 • Ouverturen für das Piano-Forte solo. Nro. 59 -Elisabeth von G. Rossini.
29 • Sanctus [and] Agnus Dei
22 • Semiramide. Overture
34 • Stabat Mater
Rubinstein, Anton
16 • Sonata for piano and cello or viola, op. 18
Ruitzy
29 • Mass Pastorale
Russell
6 • A Celebrated Introduction and Fugue
Scherbauer, K.
30 • Vesperae breves (Op. 5)
Schloesser, L.
16 • Variations Concertantes pour Piano et Violon sur un Thême de la Cenerentola Musique de J. Rossini..par L. Schloesser. Oeuv. 3.
Schmitt, Aloys
9 • Etudes pour le Piano forte par Aloïse Schmitt. Op. 16. Prémière Partie contenant des exercices préparatoires servantà acquérir une indépendance etégalité des doigts possibles, suivies de vingt Etudes
Schmitt, Jacques
9 • Marsch fürs Clavier, von J. Schmitt
20 • Var. No. 7.
19 • Variations Brillantes pour le Piano Forté avec accompagnement de deux Violons, Alto & Basse par Jacques Schmitt. Oeuvre 23.
Schneider, F.
• Jesu Mellifluus. => see: Haydn, Mass in B-flat, Box 26
Schubert, Franz
31 • Ave Maria
29 • Mass in F
Sessi, Marianne
42 • Canzonetta composta da Signora Marianne Sessi. (Nasce nel vago aprile porporea Rosa... )
Shaw, Oliver
45 • There is an hour of peaceful rest
Smith, Theodore
42 • Rondo. The Words by a Young Gentleman. Set by Theodore Smith.
Souvin, Edward
31 • Adoremus Natum
Spintler, Chr.
17 • Varsovienne
Spohr, Louis
40 • Blessed are the dead
Spontini, Gaspare (Luigi Pacifico)
12 • Ouverturen für das Piano-Forte solo. [Nro. 27,28,61]
St. Clair, C. G.
29 • Mass in G
Steibelt, Daniel
19 • Deux Sonates pour le Forte-Piano avec accompagnement de Violon et Basse (ad Libitum) composées par D. Steibelt. Oeuvre 33.
19 • Ouverture Turque pour le Clavecin ou Forté-Piano avec Violon et Violoncelle composée par Mr. Steibelt. Oeuvre 7me.
9 • Rondeau Piémontais, pour Piano-Forté, Composé par D. Steibelt.
19 • Trois Sonates d'une difficulté progressive pour Piano-Forté, avec accompagnement de Violon et Violoncelle ad libitum, composées par D. Steibelt. Oeuvre 37. Seconde éd.
Sterkel, Johann Franz Xaver
20 • III Sonates pour le Clavecin ou Piano Forte accompagnées d'un Violon et Basse. Composées par Mr. Sterkel. Oeuvre XVII. Liv. I.
Stevenson, John Andrew
• See our oars with feathered spray. => see: Mozart, Twelfth Mass, Box 24
Stradella, Alessandro
40 • Air D'Eglise (Pieta Signore)
Strauss, Johann
9 • Les Fantastiques (Die Fantasten.) Nouvelle suite de valses [by] Strauss. Op. 139.
Süssmayr, Franz Xaver
17 • Der Spiegel von Arkadien, Opera, en Duos pour Deux Flutes Traversieres arrangées par Ehrenfried. No. 9.
42 • Der Spiegel von Arkadien. Gesänge für das Clavier von Herrn Süssmayr. Nro. 13. (Seit ich so viele Weiber fah)
Thalberg, Sigismond
9 • Cinq Fantaisies pour le Piano sur des motifs des Opéras de Mozart, Meyerbeer & Bellini composées par Sig. Thalberg. Op. 10. No. 3 - Capuletti
10 • Home! Sweet Home! op. 72
Thomas, J. B.
32 • Ave maris stella
Thunder, H. G.
34 • Tantum Ergo
Tomaschek, W. J.
30 • [Requiem Mass]
30 • Messa Cantata con piena Orchestra - Fatta in Venezia
Tuckerman, S. Parkman
40 • Anthem - Sing praises to God
Umbrecht, Carl Gottleib
6 • 51 Orgelstücke
[Unidentified]
38 • An Gott. [Der du mit Weisheit... ]
31 • Asperges
31 • Ave Maria
32 • Ave Verum
• Crudeles Herodes. => see: Liber scriptus, by Ohnewald, Box 32
32 • Deo gloria
• Deus tu orum. => see: Liber scriptus, by Ohnewald Box 32
32 • Dona nobis pacem
• E viva Maria. => see: Jesu Mater, arr. by André
32 • In Festo...
32 • Lucis Creator
32 • Mater admirabilis
33 • O salutaris hostia
33 • Regina coeli
33 • Regina terrae
33 • Resurrexit
33 • Salve Regina
34 • Tantum Ergo
34 • Te Deum
34 • Te Deum
35 • Tota Pulchra
35 • Veni Creator
35 • Venite filii
35 • Vir Fideles
35 • Vivat pastor - Song of Welcome for a Bishop or Pastor
Unilau
43 • 2 Romanzen aus der Oprette Das Irrlicht.
Van Uffel, Jean
42 • L'Arbre de Noël. Melodie de Jean van Uffel. (Composée en 1583) Paroles de Mr. Ed. Thierry. Musique arrangée par Albert Grisar.
Verdi, Giuseppe
22 • Ernani. Excerpts
• Jesu Dei vivi. => see: Haydn, Mass in B-flat, Box 26
Viereck
35 • Gage d'amitie, Op. XVI [variations]
Viotti, Giovanni Battista
20 • Vingt deuxième [22nd] Concerto pour le Violon, accompagné de grand orchestre composé par J. B. Viotti.
Vogler, Georg Joseph
32 • Laudate Dominum
29 • Missa Pastorale No. 2 in E
29 • Missa Pastoritia, No. 2 in D. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland
29 • Missa Solemnis No. I. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland
24 • Missa Solennis vom Abt. Vogler. No. 1. Partitur. Nach dem hinterlassenen Original Manuscript herausgegeben.
Wade, J. Augustine
10 • I've Wandered in Dreams
Wagner, C.
6 • Die Jungfrau von Orleans
Waldteufel, Emile
16 • Always or Never Waltz
Walter, Georg Anton
16 • Trois Duos pour deux Violons par Walter. Oeuvre 7me, Livre 1.
Wanhal, Johann Baptist
13 • [Unidentified]
13 • Petites Pièces
16 • Sonata per il Piano-Forté con Violino obligato del Giovanni Wanhal. Lit:D. No. 1.
Warnitzky
46 • Horcht, Vater, horcht
Webbe, Samuel
32 • Emitte spiritum
29 • Mass in A; Kyrie, Gloria
33 • O Jesu Deus
31 • Tantum Ergo, No. 3
Weber, Carl Maria von
22 • Der Freischütz
12 • Der Freischütz - Hunting Chorus
43 • Der Freischütz. Aria
46 • Der Freischütz. Terzett con Chor
29 • Mass in G
29 • Mass. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland
Weber, Karl Maria Friedrich Ernst (Freiherr von)
12 • Ouverture to Euryanthe von C. M. von Weber.
12 • Ouverture zur grossen romantischen Oper: Euryanthe, für das Pianoforte von C. M. Weber.
12 • Ouverturen für das Piano-Forte solo. [Nro. 29,30,31,35,36]
Weigl, Joseph
42 • Aria. Je öfter ich es überlege etc. von Herrn Weigl.
22 • Les Vestales. Overture
57 • Vestales - Overture
Weiss, L.
32 • Domine dominus noster
Werner, A.
31 • Asperges
Werner, Arno (harmonizer)
38 • Forth comes the standard (Vexilla Regis), Jesus Crucified,[and] At the Cross Her Station Keeping.Harmonized by A. Werner.
Wills, J.
6 • Voluntary
Winter
• Jesu Filii Dei. => see: Haydn, Mass in B-flat, Box 26
33 • Miserere
33 • O Jesu Deus
33 • O Jesu pastor bonus
Winter, Peter
31 • Ave Maria. Trio. For the Offertory. Music by Winter.
45 • Das Unterbrochene Opferfest. Quartetto. No. 18. (Kind! willst du ruhig schlafen)
42 • Dem unterbrochen Opferfest. Aria von Hr. Capellmeister Winter. Nro. 7. (Ich war wann ich erwachte)
17 • Ouverture aus des Opera Die Zauberflöte, das Labyrinth oder der Kampf mit den Elementen fur Clavecin oder Piano Forte mit Flöte von Herrn Capelmeister Winter.
31 • Regina Coeli. Trio [for] Two Trebles and Tenor. Arranged from Winter.
Winter, Peter and Vincent Novello
31 • Jesu Fili Dei. Terzettino for Benediction from Winter and Novello.
Wittig, Carl
• Magnificat. => see: Regina coeli, by Giorza, Box 33
Wohlfahrt, Robert
9 • Sieges-Jubel. Marsch. Op. 49
Zeckwer, Richard
47 • Writing Book for Harmony Pupils. Edited for the use of the pupils of the Philadelphia Music Academy by Rich. Zeckwer.
Zelter, Carl Friedrich
43 • Feenreigen aus Schillers Musen-Almanach 1798
Zeuner, Charles
49 • 2nd Set of Tremont Quadrilles selected from Celebrated Operas, performed by Kendall & Sanborn's Band, arranged for the Piano Forte by Charles Zeuner.
55 • A Parting song
48 • Adagio[s] für die Orgel
51 • Allemande
50 • American Pot Pourri (pour le Cor)
55 • American Songs [and] American Glees
48 • Ausgeführten Choral
57 • Away! Away! Bear me away!
57 • Bagatellen für die Flöte
51 • Benedictus
55 • Blow, blow, blow, thou winter wind
57 • Boston Galopade
51 • Cantata for 4 voices
57 • Cavatina Basso, Agnus Dei
50 • Chor - Allegro
50 • Clarinet Solo with Orchestra
57 • Concerto [in C]
55 • Consiglio alla Gioventú
55 • Der Winter
49 • Eissler Quadrilles. Adapted by Francis Weiland, arranged for the Piano Forte by C. Zeuner.
50 • Fantasia
48 • Fantasia [in G]
49 • Fantasia and Polacca
48 • Fantasia for the organ